JONATHAN JEFFERY

Grapevine, TX 76051 | 817-915-3506 | jonjefferytx@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Dynamic, organized and meticulous Implementation Engineer with 6+ years' experience in the payment processing industry. Works at fast pace to meet tight deadlines. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success.

Skills

- Customer Service and Technical Support
- Strong Communication and Interpersonal Skills
- Training Implementation
- Client Needs Assessment

- Microsoft Windows and Office
- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Postman API
- CRM Software

Work History

Implementations Engineer

Mar 2022 - Current

REPAY

Fort Worth, TX

- Reviewed customer inquiries to understand project scope while managing internal delivery mechanisms.
- Designed and delivered product training for clients.
- Managed configuration, installation and troubleshooting of applications and software for clients with tight deadlines.
- Verified that every client received highest level of support, assistance, and professionalism to uphold company's commitment to service.

Customer Service Representative

Nov 2018 - Mar 2022

REPAY

Fort Worth, TX

- Coordinated with clients, management, and sales team to better understand customer needs and recommend appropriate solutions.
- Conducted training sessions for clients and team members on how to utilize different software and terminals that company offers.
- Reconciled multiple merchant accounts, including credit cards, ACH payments end of month statements, and bank statements.

Customer Service Team Leader

Jan 2017 - Nov 2018

First American Payment Systems

Fort Worth, TX

- Fostered positive employee relationships and growth through communication, training, and coaching. Lowered call errors by teammates by roughly 30%.
- Performed thorough quality checks to verify conformance to company standards of customer service.
- Conducted research on latest point-of-sale devices to test for errors and consumer use.

Education

Bachelor of Arts: Film and Video Production

May 2015

Baylor University

Waco, TX

- Tau Kappa Epsilon Fraternity Member
- Boxing Club Member

Certifications

- Web Development, Mimo December 2020
- Website Creation, Mimo June 2020